Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- EUGENE ELLIS VANN - AUTOGRAPHS, SURGERY, RETIREMENT ACTIVITIES, OBITUARIES, MEMORIAL SERVICE, CORRESPONDENCE (Box 36)
  - Retirement Activities (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Newspaper clipping about portraits painted of Eugene and Elizabeth, 1950: July 27
    Incoming correspondence to Eugene from:
    The Home Insurance Co. 1949: June 16(Walter F. Beyer) 1950: May 9(Harold V. Smith 1951: June 21(Harold Smith) 1952: June 30(J. Donald Whelehan)
    The Men’s Neighborhood Club of Leonia 1959: Mar.28(Edward A. ‘Stewart)
    National Committee for Rural Schools, Inc. 1961: Nov.6(Rae Brandstein)
    Northern Valley Consumers' Cooperative 1954: Apr.27(John M. Williams)
  - Gift of Spanish and Portuguese Books to Fairleigh Dickinson, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Vanderbilt University: The Lawson Case, 1960, Chi Chronicle Alumni letter, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F., 1962 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Obituaries, Eugene, January 6, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    (1) laminated clipping n. d.
    The Birmingham News Jan.8
    Birmingham Post-Herald Jan.8
    The New York Herald Tribune Jan.8
    The Newark(NJ)Evening News Jan.8
    The Patterson(NJ)Evening News Jan.8
    Press Journal, Englewood, NJ Jan.14
    The Record (Bergan Co.?) Jan.8
    The Vanderbilt Alumnus Jan.1965
  - Memorial Service and Guest Book (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Memorial Service: The Presbyterian Church, Leonia, NJ
    The Rev. Paul Noble, Minister (2) copies
  - Expressions of Sympathy to Elizabeth: Flowers, Telegrams, and Cards (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Flowers from: Englewood Hospital Association,
    Board of Trustees Gracie & Helen Hazel
    Helen & Bob Mary Virginia & Bob The Two Mauds(2) Ruth & Alex
    Edith & Roscoe White, Denny & Martha, Lou and Pine, Marvin & Bettie.
    Lucy & Preston Slosson, Lucy Chase, Mary Libs & All, Flora May & Edith.
    Rebecca, Collins & Anne, Clifford.
    The Bonds
    Dr. & Mrs. N. Vansant Myers
    Telegrams: Betty & Clyde
    Frances, Lissa & Debbie
    Grover, Emily Ruth & Children
    Julia, Blanton & the Boys
    Lissa
    Rebecca
    Gautreau, Gaston & Family
    Hoyler, Tony & Berta
    Robinson, Jean Lambeth(3)
    Sympathy Cards: Alex
    Alex
    Betty & Ted
    Evelyn
    American Legion Post #1
    Anderson, Inez, Holger & Elliott
    Askanas, Carol
    Barry, Mr.&Mrs.
    Beveridge, Merle
    Burton, Hattie H.
    Capitol View Stamp Club
    Cliff, Eyle
    Cloud, Al
    Cusano Family
    De Scherer, Nathan
    de Szalatuay.
    Du Bois, Kathryn & Howard
    Dwyer, Ruth
    Gallione, John & Barbara
    Gereb, Sheila & Dan
    Gordon, Mollie & Bob
    Holmes, Fred & Jane
    Kenney, Bernice
    Lefhowitz, Selina
    Lewis, Annie
    MacKenzie, Jr., R.I.&Alice
    Martin, Nathan B.
    Martinez, Mike & Josephine
    Mausner, Laura(Northern Valley Chapte United Nations Association)
    Molchan, Wavalyn C.
    Moore, Dan & Eugenia
    Nurses on Maternity 3
    Pisani, Brenda
    Rodrigues, O.R.
    Root, Lee(Mrs. Arnold)
    Saigle, Dr.&Mrs. Raymond
    Satter, Kent N.
    Spencer, Mrs. Erma
    Voskiow, Dr.&Mrs. John B.
    White, Carrie < Eddie
    Wolff, Ann & Bob
  - “The Leonia Civic Conference in Retrospect” (Box 37, Folder 18)
    American Eastern Stamp Co, Jan. 8
    Bertha H. Mar.4
    Catherine Jan.l?
    Elsie n.d.
    Enid Jan.16
    Erika Jan.10
    Ethel S. Jan.8
    Evalin n.d.
    Henry Jan.9
    Hoy Jan.16
    Jimmie (?) n.d.
    Lou Jan.14
    Margaret Jan.11
    Marjorie & Howard Jan.11
    Marjory Jan.13
    May Jan.10
    Ruth Jan.11
    Shirley Jan.18
    Susan Jan.7
    Tom Jan.8
    Adams, Alberta Jan.11
    Bailu, Bart Jan.25
    Banta, Victor D. Jan.7
    Barbash, Roslyn & Philep Jan.26
    Bash, Julian & Adelaide Mar.5
    Bingham, Ray Jan.9
    Biscaye, George E. Jan.7
    Blind, Bill Jan.20
    Bornemann, A1 Jan.15
    Bowerman, Walter G. Jan.11
    Braegger, Victor Jan.8
    Burritt, Richard Jan.19
    Burrowes, Paul Jan.11
    Burton, Hattie H. Jan.10
    Castellas, Miguel Jan.13
    Clarke, Emmy Lou(2) Jan.12
    Corker, Bea Feb.3
    Cory, David C. Jan.12
    Cowan, Content Jan.10
    Crowley, Eve Jan.8
    Crymble, Hannah Jan.7
    Davis, Ethel M.(2) n.d.
    Douds, Ella Jan.14, Feb.26
    Dowdy, Elizabeth & Wes Jan.14
    Dunlap, Evelyn Jan.11
    Empeley(?), Marshall Jan.12
    Evans, Helene R. Jan.15 Jan.21
    Farquhar, Myrtle n.d.
    Fincke, Allen W. Jan.8
    Finney, Jo & Fred Jan.11
    Gellhorn, Olga Jan.19
    Glasser, John W.H. Jan.19
    Glidden, Jr., Nathaniel Jan.9
    Gonzalez, Jose M. Jan.11
    Graves, Edith Jan.7
    Hale, Kathryn C. Feb.16
    Handley, Gertrude K. Feb.9
    Hart, Louise & David(2) Jan.8, Feb.15
    Hatcher(?), Ceislia A. Jan.18
    Hemenway, Oakley Feb.16
    Henry, Dorothy N, n.d.
    Hooks, Maud M. Jan.10
    Hutchinson, Viola Jan.22
    Hutsinpiller, Edith Feb.4
    James, Mary Bell Jan.15
    Jarrell, Saidee Jan.8
    Jones, Allie Y. Feb.12
    Kantiontz(?), C. Jan.28
    Kaps, Frank J. Jan.19
    Kean, Osmond Jan.12
    Kennedy, W.A. Jan.11
    Kester, Jr., Lee L. Jan.12
    Kiphuth, Janet Jan.20
    Kron, Arthur A. Jan.11
    Lang, Victoria Jan.11
    Leatherfee, Mary n.d.
    Lennon, Libby Mar.4
    Leon, David C. Dec.19
    Lopez, Frank & Lia Mar.16
    Ludowise, Sylvia Jan.22
    MacMillan, Wright Mar.10
    Marin, Ventura G. Jan.18
    Marsh, May n.d.
    Martins, Dudley Jan.8
    Massie, G. Edmond Feb.4
    Massie, Lucile K. Mar.6
    Merrill, Edith n.d.
    Meyer, Henry Jan.7
    Meyer, Suzanne n.d.
    Mills, George S. Jan.9
    Mitchell, James A. Jan.8
    Mohair, Ray(Mrs. Joe)(2) Jan.13, Mar.6
  - Hospital Memorials in Memory of Eugene (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Englewood Hospital Association June 14
    Book Club Members(Mrs. Vann's) n.d.
    The· Home Insurance Co.
    Knapp Charitable Trust
    Leonia Men's Bridge Club
    Medical Staff of Englewood Hospital
    Northern Valley Consumers' Cooperative Feb.ll
    Allen, Mr.&Mrs. Dudley
    Balze, Dr.&Mrs. Henry R.
    Bingham, Mr.&Mrs. J.R.
    Bose, Mr.&Mrs. Henry
    Burritt, Mr.&Mrs. Richard D.
    Cosgrove, Dr.&Mrs. Robert
    Deimel, Mrs. R.F.
    Doscher, Jack
    Fernalld, Esther L.
    Ferrall, Mr.&Mrs. Victor E.
    Fichter, Harry, Othmar & Charles
    Forsthoff, Sr., Mrs. Harry
    Forsthoff, Mr.&Mrs. Harry
    Gunn, Eileen D.
    Hart, David
    Jackman, Dr. & Mrs. J. Earl
    Leslie, Jesse B.
    Lopez, Mr.& Mrs. Frank
    Hac.Hichael ,. Gertrude
    Manton, E.A.G.
    Miller, Mrs. J. Clifford
    Mills, George s.
    Mohair, Mrs. Joe
    Nelson, Mr.&Mrs. Luther A.
    Oliver, Freda & Peter
    Parker, Jr., Charles E.
    Pendergast, Mr.& Mrs. George A.
    Robertson, Mr.& Mrs. D.P.
    Stuart, Mr.& Mrs. J. William
    Vann, Mr.& Mrs. Augustus M.
    Vann, Dr. Felix H.
    Vann, Jeanne
    Vann, Marie Y.
    Vann, Mr.& Mrs. R. Joel
    Vann, Mr.& Mrs. Robert J.
    Vann, Mr.& Mrs. Young
    Woods, John R.
    Worthington, Jr., Mr.& Mrs. Grover c.
    Edith & Children
  - Eugene's Estate, A share of stock Closing letter from the IRS, 1965: Jan.6 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- EUGENE ELLIS VANN: OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE IN BOXES 35, 36, 37 (Box 36)
  - (2) n.d. (Dear Sir) F 55-15. (1) n.d. (W.H.P. Faunce)F55-15. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - (W.H.P. Faunce)F55-15., (1) n.d. (Box 37)
  - “The Leonia Civic Conference in Retrospect” (Box 37)
  - Feb.23(William R. Shepherd), F 35-13. Mar.27 F 35-15., 1916: (Box 37)
  - July 5(Hon. Josephus Daniels), 9(Hon. Breckenridge Long) F 55-1 Oct.10(Percy A. Martin) F 35-11. Oct.18(Dr. Harry Lyman Koopman) F 55-13. Dec.31(E.A. Goff) F 55-19., 1917: (Box 37)
  - Jan.15(E.A. Goff); Apr.12(E.A. Goff) F 55-19., 1918: (Box 37)
  - Feb.17(Ginn & Co.) F 55-18. Apr.l(J.L. Cross) F 35-19. Aug.31(Percy A. Martin) F 55-11. Oct.23(J.C. Branner) F 55-10. Dec.31(William R. Shepherd) F 55-15., 1919: (Box 37)
  - Jan.27(Frederick Todd) F 55-19. July 21(Dr. Horace Williams) F 55-10. July 22(J.C. Branner) F 55-10. July 31(Ginn & Co.) F 55-18. Aug.26(H.E. Freund) F 55-19., 1920: (Box 37)
  - “The Leonia Civic Conference in Retrospect” (Box 37)
  - May 27(F.W. Latson) F 55-15., 1921: (Box 37)
  - May 3(J.J. Riley), 31(Corn Exchange Bank, 31(0.J. Campbell) F 55-19., 1923: (Box 37)
  - Apr.24(Percy A. Martin), 26(Perrin C. Cothran) F 55-11., 1926: (Box 37)
  - Nov.2(Percy A. Martin); Dec.13(Percy A. Martin), Dec.14(Frank B. Fackenthal) F 55-11. Dec.14(Louis A. Imbert), 16(Percy A. Martin) F 55-9., 1927: (Box 37)
  - Oct.24(Percy A. Martin) F 55-9., 1930: (Box 37)
  - Aug.l(Percy A. Martin) F 55-9., 1932: (Box 37)
  - Oct.6(E.A. Burlingame), 13(Ruy Lowndes) F 55-15., 1933: (Box 37)
  - Feb.9(Ruy Lowndes), 10(F.W. Latson); May 9(E.A. Burlingame), 1934: (Box 37)
  - Jan.17(Harold V. Smith) F 56-15., 1945: (Box 37)
  - Mar.25(Wilfred Kurth); May 29(Lee Whitcomb) F 56-15., 1947: (Box 37)
  - May 24-25(30 letters announcing retirement); Sept.l(Corn Exchange Bank) F 56-14. Dec.4(Harold V. Smith), 13(Federal Security Agency, Social Security Board), 13(U.S. Treasurery Dept.) F 57-10., 1948: (Box 37)
  - Jan.4(U.S. Treasurery Dept.) F 37-10., 1949: (Box 37)
  - Jan.27(Henry B. Reinhardt) F 37-10. Feb.28(IRS) F 36-14. Mar.16(Federal Security Agency); Apr.18(Social Security Board) F 37-10., 1950: (Box 37)
  - May 7(William J. Fitzpatrick) F 36-17., 1952: (Box 37)
  - Nov.17(Edward Lee Norton) F 35-2., 1955: (Box 37)
  - Mar.7(Alben W. Barkley) F 35-24., 1956: (Box 37)
  - Jan.19(Dr. Guy E. Snavely), 28(Dr. Guy E. Snavely) F 34-2., 1957: (Box 37)
  - (?) 2(H. Ben Englebert) F 35-2., 1958: (Box 37)
  - Apr.6(H.Ben Englebert); Apr.7(Henry King Stanford) F 35-2., 1960: (Box 37)
  - Feb.14(John F. Kennedy) F 35-24., 1963: (Box 37)
  - Aug.1(Walter Bowerman) F 35-24. Nov.19(Dudley Wilson) F 35-25., 1964: (Box 37)
  - ELIZABETH VANN PAPERS BOX 58 - EUGENE ELLIS VANN: DATE BOOKS, DIARIES, EXPENSE BOOKS (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Date books (30) 1924-1963.
    Diaries (8) 1958-1963.
    Expense books (21)
    Address book (1)
  - EUGENE ELLIS VANN DIAHIES & DIARY INDEX (Box 37, Folder 39)
    Diary Index (1) 1921-1948.
    Diaries:
    1921-22
    1935
    1940
    1941
    1944
    1947
    1948
    1949
    1950
    1952
    1953
    1954
    1955
    1956
    1957
    Diary of European Trip (1)
    1952-1952.
- EUGENE V ANN - TRAVEL LITERATURE (Box 39)
  - Canada. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Jamaica. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - England. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - France. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Paris. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Holland. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Italy. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Southeast Asia. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Spain. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - United States. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Books
    All About Spain. Georgia Long.
    New Trails in Old Spain. Vernon Howe Bailey.
- FELIX HUFFMAN VANN: OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FAMILY, AND FRIENDS. (Box 40)
  - n.d.(Grandpa), (Grandmother), (?). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Aug.2(Grandpa)., 1916: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - June 13(Collins Denny, Jr.), 28(Grandpa)., 1918: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Nov.8(Grandma), 27(Grandpa)., 1919: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Nov.15(Grandma)., 1920: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.10(Grandma)., 1924: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.16(Grandmother)., 1927: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Mar.13(Grandmother), 29(Grandfather), 30(Lucy)., 1930: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - May 1( Bishop Collins Denny), 31 (Grandparents); Dec.25(Grandparents). F 1., 1933: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - (Mr.& Mrs. Deimel); Aug.23(Grandfather); Sept.20(Grandparents)., 1934: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.19(Grandparents); Feb.3(Lucy); June 9(Grandmother & Grandfather Denny), 21(Mother May), 21(Lucy Chase, Mary Libby, Flora May & Edith Slosson), 24(Collins Denny, Jr. & Rebecca)., 1935: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - May 25(Mrs. Collins Denny)., 1938: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dec.22(Grandfather)., 1939: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dec.26(Grandfather). F 2., 1941: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - July 25(Grandfather); Aug.9(Lucy); Sept.16(Lucy); Oct.l(Grandfather), 12(Grandfather), 24(Dorothea Deimel Vann), 30(Lucy); Nov.3(Slossons), 10(Bishop Collins Denny), 18(Edith White).; (l)n.d.(Collins Denny, Jr.)., 1942: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Mar.3(Elizabeth Whitfield), 3(Dorothea); May 7(Edith White): July (Edith White); Oct.29(Margaret Dixon); Nov.3(Lucy); Dec.19(Edith) F 3., 1943: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.4(Edith White), 24(Edith White); Apr.2(Lucy & Preston Slosson), 7(Edith & Roscoe White) (Collins & Rebecca Denny); May 17(Richard D. Vann); June 14(Dorothea), 20(Collins & Rebecca), 24(Dorothea); July 14(Dorothea); Aug.23(Edith White); Oct.27(Collins & Rebecca); Nov.4(Lucy); Dec.13(Eugene N. Vann), 30(Lucy & Preston), 30(?)., 1944: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.30(Lucy & Preston); Mar.15(Edith White); May 13(Lucy & Preston); Aug.5(Lucy Chase, Lucy & Preston Slosson)., 1945: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.1(Edith White)., 1946: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Feb.8(Slossons); Aug.15 (Dorothea & Richard Vann). F 3, 1947: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.28(Parents). F 3., 1948: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - June 29(Dorothea); Jan.2(31ossons). F 4., 1950: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Feb.4(Dorothea)., 1951: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dec.28(Margaret Dixon)., 1953: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.10(Edith & Roscoe White)., 1957: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.20(Aunts, Uncles, Cousins); Dec.27(Edith & Roscoe White), 27(Margaret Dixon)., 1959: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Aug.25(Parents). F 4., 1960: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.7(Edith & Roscoe White)., 1961: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Aug.1( Richard Vann); Nov.6(Lucy & Preston)., 1966: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Feb.2(Richard), 9(Sichard), 24(Edith White); Apr.8(Richard); May 3(Richard); June 18(Richard), 22(Dorothea); Aug.22(Dorothea); Dec.21(Richard)., 1969: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - April ?(Elizabeth Whitfield); June 30(Richard); July 20(Dorothea); Sept.21(Edith & Roscoe White)., 1970: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.11(Richard & Sheppy Vann); July 23(Dorothea)., 1971: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.2(Lucy & Preston Slosson & Edith White); Aug.27(Dick, Sheppy & Mother); Sent.2(Dick & Sheppy), 24(Dick Sc Sheppy); Oct.16(Dick & Sheppy). Nov.5(Dick & Sheppy; F 4., 1972: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.9(Edith & Roscoe), 21(Richard & Sheppy); Feb. if (Richard, Sheppy & Mom), 20(Richard & Sheppy); Mar.25(Richard & Sheppy); July 1(Dorothea, Mo, Richard & Sheppy), 15(same); Sept.4(Lucy), 20(Lucy & Preston); Oct.27(Mom, Richard, Sheppy & Gene)., 1973: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.31(Dick & Sheppy); July 13(Dick, Sheppy, Gene & Mike); Aug.22(Dorothea), 22(Edith); Sept.2(Richard & Sheppy); Dec.22(Richard & Sheppy)., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Feb.23(Dick & Sheppy); Apr..6(Edith & Mom);, June 22(Dick, Sheppy. Gene & Mike); Sept.l(Dick & Sheppy); Nov.9(Elizabeth); Dec.21(Edith & Mom)., 1975: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.l(Dick & Sheppy)., 1976: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - May 9(Preston Slosson). F 5., 1977: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FRIENDS - FOLDER 6 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - n.d.(Grandpa), (Grandmother), (?)., Dec.(Bob & Mary ?).; 1934: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Oct.20(Tom ?)., 1944: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.19(Tom ?), 1945: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sept.8(Willard)., 1973: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.30(Thomas E. Gaughan)., 1975: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jan.9(President Gerald Ford), 9(Senator Clifford P. Case), 9(Hon. Harrison A. Williams)., **1976: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Apr.l(Henry & Betty Swint), 2(Mrs. A1 Wilson). F 6., 1978: (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FAMILY - Folders 7-23 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Betty ?, 1976: Apr.3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Libba ?, 1973: Jan.29 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Libby ?, n.d. F 7. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Deimel, Christine., 1968: July 3. 1969: June 20. F 8. (Box 40, Folder D)
  - Denny, Collins (Bishop). 1940'- May 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Denny, Lucy(Mrs. Collins). (3)n.d. 1922: ?; July 3,6,12,18,23,31. F 9. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Denny, Collins, Jr. & Rebecca Wedding invitation. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1926: Dec.6. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1930: May 14. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1932: Aug.8,15. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1934: Sept.15. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1942: June 16. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1953: Jan.9. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1974: Feb.12. F 10. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Denny, Collins, III., 1970: June 12. F 11. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dixon, Margaret Denny (Mrs. John W."Jack")., 1942: Nov.13. 1969: Jan.13(from Jack), (l)n.d.(from Jack). F 12. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Slosson, Lucy Denny. (Box 40, Folder S)
    1926: May 30.
    1928: May 11.
    1930: Mar.2(Lucy & Preston); June 10.
    1933: Apr.28; June 4.
    1934: Dec.20.
    1935: Jan.19.
    1939: Apr.15.
    1950: Apr.6, 10(from Lucy Chase). F 13.
  - Slosson, May Preston., 1926: June 14. F 13. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Slosson, Preston., 1926: Aug.25. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1927: Jan.6; Feb.16; June ?.
    1929: Apr.24.
    1935: Apr.9; May 28. F 13.
  - Wueliner, Wilhelm. ?:, Jan.8. F 13. (Box 40, Folder W)
  - Vann, Dorothea Deimel. (Box 40, Folder V)
    1966: Aug.31; Sept.5.
    1967: Aug.17.
    1969: June 18,23,27; July 2,5,7,18; Aug.11,26,30; Sept.2.
    1970: July 13.
    1971: July 13; Aug.29; (l)n.d.
    1973: July 6.11; Aug.25,29.
    1974: June 9123; Aug.23,26,29.
    1975: July 2,12; Aug.13.
    1976: June 2b; July 12; Aug.16,21,25,28; Sept.l. F 15. Vann, Clyde H.(wife - Ruth).
    1930: May 29. F 14.
  - Vann, Ruth., 1933: June 21. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 1934: Feb.4; Dec.22. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 1942: Nov.28. F 14. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Vann, (Rev.)Felix A. & Mrs. Vann., (l)n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1926: June 4. 1927: Feb.28.
    1930: Jan.20; Apr.24; Aug.13.
    1937: Jan.12; Apr.13; (l)n.d.
    1944: Feb.28. F 16.
  - Vann, Joel & Katherine., 1940: Jan.l. F 17. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Vann, Richard Deimel & Mary Shepherd( "Sheppy"). (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1969: June 5.
    1973: Feb.18; Mar.25: Apr.11,14; June 17,24
    Aug.26; Sept.3,H(Elizabeth Vann, Grandmother); Oct.l; Nov. 8(Elizabeth V.), 12,2§(Elizabeth V.). 1975: April ?,28; May 20(Elizabeth V.); June 29
    Aug.31; Sept.?,8; Dec.13. F 18.
  - White, Collins Denny & Martha. (Box 40, Folder W)
    1932: Mar.26. 1935: Jan.14. 1943: Mar.27.
    1974: Feb.12. F 19.
  - White, Edith Denny & Roscoe. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1922: July 16.
    1923: July 17.
    1927: Feb.3,19.
    1929: Jan.5.
    1930: Mar.24; June 2.
    1933: June 23.
    1934: Mar.19; Sept.13; Dec.31,31(from Roscoe); (l)n.d. 1943: May 3.
    1962: Apr.11.
    1965: Aug.10.
    1967: Feb.17.
    1968: Jan.26; (l)n.d.
    1970: Aug.27.
    1973: Dec.17, ?.
    1975: Mar.29; Apr.9; Dec.29.
    1976: Jan.6; Oct.26.
    1977: Jan.10,11,14,15,25; Feb.8,22. F 20.
  - Whitfield, Elizabeth Dixon & Theodore. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1930: Jun 2 11. 1935: June 3. 1938: Jan.18.
    1940: Jan.19. 1944: Mar.17. 1940: Sept.13(Theodore). F 21.
  - Winfree, "Lou" White. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    1934: Dec.28. 1938: Jan.17. 1943: Jan.18.
    1972: Dec.?(Marc to Gene). F 22.
  - Winfree, R. Westwood("Pine")., 1970: June I?. 1973: ?; Oct.11. F 22. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Others:
    James, Mary Bell. 1977: May 21.
    Krebs, Elizabeth 0. 1971: June 26.
    Maier, Tim. (l)n.d.
    Libba ?. 1976: June 16. F 23.
  - INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FRIENDS - FOLDER 24 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Assistant Secretary of State., 1945: Feb.7. F. 24. (Box 40, Folder A)
  - Bodet(?), Bob & Mary. 1945: Jan.26. F 24. (Box 40, Folder B)
  - Bonnieburn, Anne S., 1942: Sept.23. F. 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Brown, George A., 1977: May 26. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Casey, Tom., 1944: Sept. 17. 1945: Jan. 1,15. F 24:. (Box 40, Folder C)
  - Cosgrove, Robert Allison., 1942: Oct.25. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Easton, Jean., 1975: Jan.3. F 24. (Box 40, Folder E)
  - Forster, Roger., 1973: July 22. F 24. (Box 40, Folder F)
  - Kiehl, Robert. 1973: May 26. F 24. (Box 40, Folder K)
  - McCloskey, Margaret & Boyd, Helen Elizabeth., 1909: Mar.20. F 24. (Box 40, Folder M)
  - Mathison, A., 1926: Jan.20. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Mikee(?), M., (l)n.d. F £4. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Parker, Roy T., 1975: ?; May 19(letter to Pres. Ford.). F 24. (Box 40, Folder P)
  - Partridge, Cora B., 1943: May 7. 1960: July ?. F_24:. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ritchie, W., 1939: Oct.10. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Rowbotham, J. & May., 1940: Dec.21. 1944: Dec.7. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1977: June 10,20,22(2). F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Smith-Wright, Betsy., 1977: June 17; Dec.9. F 24. (Box 40, Folder s)
  - Smith, George V., 1973: Oct.7. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Tucker, H.C., 1951: Dec.?. F 24. (Box 40, Folder T)
  - Vander ?, Sandy., 1944: Nov.27. F 24. (Box 40, Folder V)
  - Zastos, G., (l)n.d. F 24. (Box 40, Folder Z)
  - OTHERS, (l)n.d. ?. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - M(?)-woman who took care of Dick., 1957: Feb.12 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dorothea & Carlos., 1975: Jan.20. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Leroy ?, 1975: Apr.19. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Monte ?, 1937: Jan.31. F 24. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1935: Jan.9(Mrs. Collins Denny). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - June ?(Parents-Mr.&Mrs. Deimel), 21(Lucy & Preston Slosson). 24(Roscoe & Edith White), ?(1 p.), 26(Deimels), ?(1 p.), 30(Deimels); July 8(Deimels), 12(Aunt Mamie Chapman), 12(Aunt Grace), 12 (Edith White), 14(Deimels), 15(Deimels), 21-23(Deimels), 29(Deimels); Aug. 6(Deimels), 16(Deimels), 20(Deimels). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1944: Jan.3(Elizabeth & "Tedo" Whitfield). F 25. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - DOROTHEA DEIMEL VANN: INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FAMILY (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Denny, Rebecca(Mrs. Collins, Jr.) ?:, Feb.21. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Vann, David & Lil., (l)n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - White, Collins Denny P. Martha., 1967: May 24(2). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Winfree, Lou White., 1967: May 18. F 26. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - * Add to Folder 5 - Correspondence from Felix to Family:, 1978: Oct.15(Edith): Nov.26(Family) 1979: June 11(Edith); Sept.3(Edith). (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Felix to Henry Swint and Essie Samuels - Vanderbilt Centennial History:, 1976: Mar.22(Essie); June 1(Essie). 1977: Apr.10(Henry); May 12(Essie); Dec.18(Essie). 1978: Jan.8(Essie); Feb.4(Essie), 9(Essie), Feb.8(Mar ce Wolfe), 8(Frank Grish m), 28(Essie); Mar.7(Essie); Apr.1(Essie), 1(Henry), 25(Essie); June 8(Essie); Oct.31(Essie). 1979: June 17(Essie), 17(Henry). 1980: Jan.20(Essie). (Box 40, Folder 6)
- FELIX HUFFMAN VANN - ESSAYS, SCHOOLS, WEDDING CORRESPONDENCE, EUROPEAN TRIP (Box 41)
  - Essays and Scout Reports, 1917 - 1927 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Schools Attended (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Incoming Correspondence from Otis W. Caldwell 1917: July 3(to Elizabeth)
    1923: Mar.13(to Elizabeth)
    1932: Apr.12(to Preston W. Slosson)
    1934: Aug.8(Felix)
    From Elizabeth Vann to Mr. Frayer
    1930: Feb.15
  - Letters of Introduction for Felix(for European trip, 1934 From: Austin(?), Harry(3) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Dickinson, Robert L.(2)
    Glass, Carter(Senator)(2)
    Hull, Cordell
    Kenney, Edward A.
    Rhuet ?
    Ritchie. W.T.(or L.)(Zf)
    Roper(?), Daniel(Secretary of Commerce)(2)
    VonRooyen, Clennel(?)
    List of names and hospitals
  - Wedding: Felix Huffman Vann and Dorothea Deimel 1935: June 13 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    (1) Photograph of Dorothea Newspaper clippings
    Trip to Richmond, VA (l)n.d.
    Engagement
    Bergen Evening News. 1935: May 29 New York Times. 1935: May 9 Sailing to England
    Bergen Evening Record. 1935: June 5 Leonia Life. 1935: May 31 Wedding Announced
    Bergen Evening Record. 1935-* June 13 (1) n.d.
    Wedding Announcements (3)
    At Home Cards (3)
    "Marriages in Great Britain"
    Engraved printing plates (2)
  - Lists of Wedding Gifts. Cards from Gifts (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Wedding Cards, Telegrams and Letters, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Cards:
    Hoffman, Mignon Woodard Scales, Frances
    Seales(or Scales), Cecil & Frances Weeks, D.C.
    Telegrams:
    Betty & Donals June 5
    Aberdeen. Mrs. Clark June 13
    Aulttess(or Faultless), F. June 13
    Collins & Rebecca June 13